chinatraveldepot.com 2008-12-21

# Privacy and Security Policy, China Travel Depot

**What does ChinaTravelDepot do with the information collected?**

**We do not collect personal information about you when you browse the site. We collect any kind of personal information when you give it to us in order to deal efficiently and properly with your reservation forChina Tours, City Breaks, China Flights,  China Hotels.**

We will need to collect personal information about you to handle your booking as smoothly as possible, especially ChinaTravelDepot is the only Online Travel Agent in China offering real-time reservation and real-time confirmation service to make your trip to China easy, affordable and safe.

This information may include such details as your name as shown in the passport, your home address, your phone number, your travel insurance status and your credit card details. The information is required when we have to offer the information to the relevant service suppliers such as airlines for your flight ticket reservation, hotels for your accommodation, land service agents for the transfers and tours, emergency contact with your appointed insurance company, payment to ChinaTravelDepot to secure your booking etc.

We disclose your information to third parties only for the purpose of completing your transaction with us, providing the above services to you and for the purpose of associated administration and obtaining professional and efficient advice.

ChinaTravelDepot may use the information provided by you to contact you about your holiday directly for the purpose of reminding punctual payment, offering travel advice, customizing your trip to your full satisfaction and enjoyment.

When you view our site by linking from another web page we may store the name of that web page for purposes of internal administration. Also please note that any contact with CYTS, either online or by telephone, may be recorded for training and monitoring purposes.

**What is a 'cookie' and how does ChinaTravelDepot use cookies?**

Cookies are small files which are sent to your browser (for example Internet Explorer or Netscape) and stored on your computer's hard disk. They only identify your computer and not you personally. Like most websites, we store cookies on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to gain information on the user of our services. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browsers to prevent that.

Cookies help speed up the booking process so that you do not need to re-type the same information again and again. We use cookies to measure site usage such as entry and exit points of visitors, how many people visit a certain section or page and details of searches performed and related information. If you are making a purchase we will also use cookies to keep track of the transaction from one page to the next. Other than this, we do not store your password or any other information in the cookie, or use it for any other purpose.

**How do I know if there is any change of the privacy policy?**

Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be made to this page. Your continued use of this site will constitute your agreement to the changed Terms and Conditions of using this site.

**What about the other sites you link to?**

ChinaTravelDepot, its employees, contractors, agents, and owners are not responsible for the privacy policies or content of any websites which it may link to.

**Security and Data Protection information**  
  
**We have taken all reasonable steps to have in place appropriate security measures to protect your information.**  
**All personal information is stored in secure databases at secure addresses to prevent unauthorized access.**

when booking online, we encrypt your personal details and use secure servers for your payment. This means any information you provide to us remains private as it travels over the internet. We use SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology with 128-bit encryption. Just look out for the Verisign symbol in your browser window on the Payment Details page. This indicates a secure area and you can complete your credit/debit card details with confidence.

We must pass the information on to the relevant suppliers of your travel arrangements such as airlines, hotels, transport companies etc. The information may also be provided to security or credit checking companies, public authorities such as customs/immigration if required by them, or as required by law.

Please be aware that any of your information held by the airlines will be available to the authorities.

Moreover, we will not pass any information onto any person not responsible for part of your travel arrangements. This applies to any sensitive information that you give to us such as details of any disabilities, or dietary/religious requirements. In making this booking, you consent to this information being passed onto the relevant persons).

You are entitled to a copy of the information held by us. If you would like to see this please contact us. We may make a small charge for this.

By disclosing your personal information to us using this website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by ChinaTravelDepot as stated in this Privacy Policy. 

ChinaTravelDepot may also use this information to contact you with details of other products and services offered by ChinaTravelDepot. If you would prefer your information not to be used in this way, you should specify your preference on the Member Sign Up page or Reservation page indicating this. If you like to change your preference, want any further information or have any queries, please contact us at: 

E-mail address: webmaster@Chinatraveldepot.com

Toll Free Call Center: 888-598-2008.

Fax:0086-10-58158827

Postal address:

E-Travel Department of China CYTS Tours Holding Co,.Ltd

19th floor, CYTS Plaza, No.5 Dongzhimen South Avenue, Dongcheng District, Beijing, China 100007
